[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Brian"]}, "docId": "110826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 39, "question": "Can you hear me OK?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 40, "answer": "I can, Brian.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 72, "question": "Is that right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 73, "answer": "That is absolutely correct.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 86, "question": "What's the probability right now, Chad, if these charts are accurate of this doing a direct hit on New York City?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 87, "answer": "It's not a doomsday scenario.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Chad", "New York City"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CC", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 117, "question": "Are they leaving?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 118, "answer": "We are stubborn and resilient but we know when we have to go.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VB", "POS", "NN", "IN", "TO", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 149, "question": "How would you describe the mood of people on the streets in New York right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 150, "answer": "I think it's let's get down to business.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 174, "question": "What is the sense you're getting about the reality of this hurricane and in particular a direct hit on New York City?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 175, "answer": "Well, obviously, it's a very serious storm.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York City"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "CD", "NNS", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 193, "question": "Is that a likely prospect, do you think from everything you're now looking at?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 194, "answer": "Well, in a worse case scenario, 12 feet is possible.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Office of Emergency Management", "FEMA"], "LOCATION": ["New York City", "New York"]}, "docId": "110826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 206, "question": "What is your view from a military point of view?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 207, "answer": "Well, as a partner with New York City, Office of Emergency Management, of course, in the state of New York, the FEMA regions.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 220, "question": "Yes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 221, "answer": "I'm going to have to leave there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 236, "question": "Have you been personally briefing him on Irene?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBN", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 237, "answer": "Yes, we have.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Irene"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "NNS", "CC", ",", "RB", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 240, "question": "Are you beginning to feel now that it's almost inevitable that New York City, for example, will take a direct hit?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 241, "answer": "There's going to impacts and, again, the hurricane center has said that this forecast track is pretty much not going to change.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York City"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 247, "question": "I mean, not that anybody would possibly blame you for doing that, but some people are suggesting as a slight overreaction this time to make sure that that kind of thing couldn't possibly happen again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "IN", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "IN", ",", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 248, "answer": "Well, I don't know about that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York City"]}, "docId": "110826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "WRB", "RB", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 256, "question": "Is it structural damage or is it from potential flooding?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 257, "answer": "I think, really, the concern in New York City is going to be how much storm surge we get.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 263, "question": "For people not in those sections, is it sensible now to be thinking about getting out of there if you can?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "RB", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "EX", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "."], "aSentId": 264, "answer": "Well, I think that's a decision that's case by case.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "CC", "WP", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 272, "question": "Do you feel like you're on top of it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 273, "answer": "Well, again, I look at this and what the team here has worked for to get ready.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["U.S."]}, "docId": "110826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "WP", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "How does this work?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "Well, when we talk about disasters and we'll just talk about what government is doing when you do have disasters that are declared by the president, it is paid for by the U.S. taxpayers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNPS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 294, "question": "Are you getting encouraging signs that evacuation and so on are being taken up by New Yorkers?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "IN", "VBP", "VBG", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "aSentId": 295, "answer": "UGATE: Yes, I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New Yorkers"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 309, "question": "Professor Coch, you think that maybe New Yorkers having been through so much may not be that keen to evacuate?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "NNP", "NNPS", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "RB", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 310, "answer": "Well, I don't think that they take things seriously.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Coch"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 338, "question": "What is your gut feeling from everything you've been hearing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 339, "answer": "My gut feeling it won't be as bad because I think the storm will start as it starts to shear as it moves over the colder water, because it's not moving fast enough.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 347, "question": "Finally, if you would give me a one word answer -- if you're in New York now, should you leave?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "CD", "NN", "NN", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 348, "answer": "If you're living under an altitude of 30 feet, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 354, "question": "Brian, can you hear me and what is going on now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 355, "answer": "I can hear you, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 366, "question": "What does it feel like right now, for you, standing in the middle of this thing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 367, "answer": "Well, you know it's exhilarating and frightening at the same time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 386, "question": "What would you imagine would happen there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "MD", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 387, "answer": "I think they are going have a lot of problems.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York City", "New York City"]}, "docId": "110826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", ":", "RB", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "RB", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 406, "question": "What's your take on it, with everything you knowing right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 407, "answer": "Piers, with everything I know right now -- again, this is a storm that because we haven't had anything like this in New York City, New York City needs to take seriously, and indeed it does.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 427, "question": "If you were in New York right now, would you leave the city?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "RB", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 428, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["East Coast"]}, "docId": "110826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "RB", "JJ", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 455, "question": "What is your reading of what we're witnessing here with Hurricane Irene?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 456, "answer": "Well, I think what makes this storm really scary is just the population density on the East Coast.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "CD", "TO", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 473, "question": "If you were in the city now, would you leave?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 474, "answer": "I would probably get out a topographic map and draw a line where there is probably 25 to 30 feet and stay higher than that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "PERSON": ["Irene"]}, "docId": "110826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 491, "question": "What can you tell me what's is going on right now in your state?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "WP", "VBZ", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 492, "answer": "Right now, Piers, what's happening is that the window for preparation time is really coming to a close, as we anticipate the arrival of Irene.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", ":", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 505, "question": "Are people right to be as concerned as they are sounding?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "RB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 506, "answer": "'MALLEY: People are absolutely right to be concerned about this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 527, "question": "Are you fearing a similar kind of catastrophe that we saw in Katrina, if this hits New York?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 528, "answer": "Well, it could happen, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Katrina", "New York"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 535, "question": "Do you think lessons have been learned enough to prevent anything like Katrina happening again?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 536, "answer": "I think government certainly has changed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 548, "question": "But if there is a direct hit on somewhere like New York City, this is going very serious, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 549, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York City"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 564, "question": "What is the simple answer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 565, "answer": "The simple answer, Piers, is yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 570, "question": "If the hurricane hits somewhere like New York, and there is substantial damage and lots of flooding and so on, if you're safe, is it better to stay off the cell phone network, so that you can allow people who need help to get it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "CC", "RB", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJR", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 571, "answer": "Well, I would say this, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Verizon"]}, "docId": "110826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "RB", ",", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", ":", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 579, "question": "What happens if the storm is so strong that it starts smashing down your infrastructure in terms of towers and so on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 580, "answer": "Well, generally, again, the best thing we can do for -- in preparation for a hurricane is to build a foundational network, which we do at Verizon, that's built on reliability and redundancy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Chad"]}, "docId": "110826pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "VBG", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 609, "question": "Piers?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 610, "answer": "Well, it's a very worrying situation, Chad.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]